And. of course.
I set it to Icelandic time
because we share a love
of the aurora borealis. Gordy.
And you have no idea how to tell time.
Great gift. Dad.
Way to think things through.
Somehow. you'd think that a man
who can send a rocket into space
would be able to manage
a halfway decent birthday present.
Nope.
You know. Gordy.
all things considered.
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
Aw.
Hey. Gordy. Surprise!
Wow! Now. there's a gift!
Here you go. Gordy. Happy birthday!
Oh. beautiful. Haley.
Now the weather. Sure to be a windy one.
We have a high-wind warning
for the LA County coast and valleys.
with some clouds sure to come in
around 10:00 a.m.
And even though the high-gust warning
will. um. expire mid to late morning.
you'll still want to keep...
The search
for a group of missing hikers
is set to resume this morning
just outside Agua Dulce.
The tour group went out two days ago
on the Pacific Crest Trail...
but didn't come back
as expected that night.
Crews started searching yesterday...
Traffic is already backed up
due to an accident on the southbound 101.
It is 7:44 with Bo and Ives.
Bang.
Whoa. Come on.
Down. down.
Down. down. down.
Bang!
Yes! Good boy.
Up. up. up.
Up! Up. up.
Gotta keep our heads up
out the clouds on this one.
I know.
Now. we land this...
yeah. like Six-Guns...
I mean. we really
put on a show. well.
you know they gotta
bring us back for the sequel.
Mm-hmm.
Well. we sure as hell ain't
gotta sell no more horses.
So. just execute.
and we ain't got no more problems. Mmm.
You good?
Where your sister?
What's that about?
She supposed to be here.
Yeah.
Goddamn it.
Thought I told you
to fix the damn walker.
You hear that?
Pops!
- Come on. come on. Pop.
- Firefly.
- What else? What else?
- Ghost.
Uh-huh.
Beethoven.
Uh-huh. uh-huh.
- Commodore.
- Yeah.
Virgil.
You good. You good.
You good. man.
- Ghost.
- You good. you good. you good.
Pops?
- Lucky.
- Pops?
- Commodore.
- Pops? Pops!
OJ. Oh. Hi. horsie.
Hey. hey. hey.
Don't look him in the eyes. please.
Okay.
You ready to do the safety meeting?
Uh. I'm gonna need. like. five.
Um. my team's almost here.
Your team's not here? Okay. hold.
Sorry. I got the horse guy
talking to me too. What's up?
- Safety meeting.
- Copy.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Miss Bonnie Clayton on set.
Here she is. everybody.
Take a look at all of that.
Fynn. this is OJ.
our horse trainer.
You remember these guys
from Flash Point.
Yeah. Hi.
Uh...
Your name is OJ?
Yeah. Otis Junior.
Oh.
Uh...
Where's the other guy?
The... The senior guy?
Dude. he died.
About six months ago.
A bunch of random shit
fell out of a plane.
So I guess we're stuck
with Junior over here.
- No.
- Yeah.
Okay. Fuck.
Great. Uh. Ant. how we lookin'?
Yeah. good.
if we're selling a horse's ass.
That's. uh.
legendary cinematographer
Antlers Holst over here.
everybody.
- Let's go ahead and spin the horse.
- But you had said "hold." so...
And now I'm saying "spin." Let's go.
Great. And while that's spinning.
can we get makeup?
Let's get makeup
for Miss Bonnie Clayton. please.
Hold on.
- Step away from the back. please.
- They told me to come here.
Good call. OJ. Um. tell you what.
let's do a quick safety meeting.
Guys. this is OJ.
our horse trainer.
Take it away.
Kill the music. please.
My name is OJ. Uh.
I think my sister's gonna be here
in a minute.
Little louder. please.
We can't hear you in the back.
I said we are animal wranglers
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
and. uh.
did you know the very first. uh...
Hey. yo!
Excuse me. Sorry.
I'm so sorry about that.
Didn't mean to do that. Sorry. brother.
- Safety meeting.
- Yeah.
Hello! How y'all doing?
Sorry for the tardiness.
My name is Emerald. That's OJ.
and we are your animal wranglers today
with Haywood Hollywood Horses.
Now. did you know that
the very first assembly of photographs
in sequential order
to create a motion picture
was a two-second clip
of a Black man on a horse?
Yes. it was. Yes. it was. Look it up.
Now. I know you guys know
Eadweard Muybridge.
the grandfather of motion pictures.
who took the pictures
that created that clip.
But does anybody know the name
of the Black jockey that rode the horse?
No.
Nope?
I mean. the very first stuntman.
animal wrangler
and movie star all rolled into one.
and there is literally no record of him.
That man was a Bahamian jockey
that went by the name
of Alistair E. Haywood.
And he is my great-great-grandfather.
- Great.
- There's another "great" grandfather.
That's why back
at the Haywood Ranch.
as the only Black-owned horse trainers
in Hollywood. we like to say.
"Since the moment pictures could move.
we had skin in the game."
All right. Let's get into some. uh.
safety precautions
while we're on set. shall we?
Number one: Please refrain
from making any loud noises.
sudden movements.
and keep your cell phones off.
We'd really appreciate that.
Two: If you see anything
that looks or feels unsafe.
contact me. OJ
or your second in chain-of-command.
And three:
Let's have a great shoot!
Uh. and I'm Emerald Haywood.
I direct. write. produce. act.
♪ I do a little singing on the side ♪
Uh. motorcycles. baby.
Look. I-I make a mean grilled cheese.
If you're looking for crafty.
just holler at me.
Okay. That was great.
That was a lot.
Uh. let's do a rehearsal.
Yeah? Rehearsal?
Rehearsal. we should.
We should do one. Rehearsing.
I think... I think he might need a break.
Yeah. we'll rehearse one
first. and then break. yeah?
Well. I'm ready to do one.
OJ. she's ready to do one.
Tell the horse
we're ready to do one.
VFX. can we get the ball in here
while we have a sec?
- Em.
- VFX.
Uh. and. OJ. you can step off.
- Step out. Step off. Uh. step out.
- Yeah. yeah.
- Em.
- What's the horse's name?
- Uh. Lucky.
- Lucky?
- Is he?
- VFX!
Yeah. Em!
- Uh. OJ. let's step off.
- You calling me?
Hey. what did I tell you about that?
If she can't get near the horse.
what are we doing here?
Hey. hey. hey!
- Whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Medic!
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
Are you okay?
Look. maybe it's just too soon.
It's not the gig. Not ready yet. Right?
- We need it. man.
- I know.
Your dad left an enormous hole.
I know that.
But don't worry.
There'll be others.
All right? I'm sorry.
- And just tell her sorry.
- Sorry.
Thank you for the opportunity.
Come on. now.
Oh. where's VFX?
All right. You got it.
So. where am I dropping you?
I'ma go up with you.
I need to get some shit.
My lil girl said. you know.
I could crash at her place
so I'll be gone in the morning.
So I'm gonna
drive you back tomorrow?
I can find a ride.
But. I mean. like.
can I get "fun OJ" out this bitch?
'Cause this wack-ass OJ is really
making me feel like I'm not loved.
Is that how you want
your little sister to feel?
What happened to Gold Rush?
Gold Rush went bankrupt.
It's been this for three years.
Damn.
Howdy. folks.
Welcome to Jupiter's Claim.
Cowboys
and cowgirls. just a little heads-up.
Join us Fridays at 5:30 p.m.
for the brand-spankin'-new
Jupiter's Claim Star Lasso Experience.
- Oh. shit.
- Come on.
I'm sorry. y'all. I'm sorry.
Photobomb!
Lucky.
Hang tight. I'll be back.
How many you sold?
How many?
Ten.
You sold ten of Pops' horses?
I'm gonna get 'em back.
- Can you stay out here?
- Why?
I'm developing a business relationship.
and you're a liability right now.
How am I a liability?
How are you a...
Don't promote your fucking
side shit on the job.
Oh. my God.
Actor. singer. dancer.
seamstress. motorcyclist.
You wanna promote something?
Promote this business.
No. OJ. No.
First of all. that's not my side shit.
This is.
And second of all.
if anybody's a liability...
Fuck you.
No. fuck you.
Hi there.
It's Amber again from Jupe's Claim.
It does look like
we were able to squeeze out
a couple of extra press passes
for the upcoming friends
and family preview.
Oh. No apology necessary.
This is in reference to the biggest.
bestest. brand-new live show
we have coming up here
at the park.
Come in.
OJ. Thanks for coming up.
How you doing?
This is my sister. Em.
Hi there.
So. uh...
who'd you bring me?
Uh. Lucky.
He's my second-best horse.
you know. uh.
but he lost focus. so. uh...
I mean. I did too.
but I can't fire myself.
- That's good.
- Hey. hey.
Hold up. This you?
You literally the Asian kid
from Kid Sheriff?
- Em. Em. Em...
- No. it's okay.
Yeah. I was. uh... I was Lil Jupe.
Ah. dude. you were literally my favorite.
You mind if I get a picture real quick?
Hey. you mind if we talk?
Yes. Of course.
Please. browse away.
Su casa es mi casa.
Thank you. I sure will.
Um. so.
same deal. yeah? Eleven. five?
- Yeah. thank you.
- That's 3D. Yeah.
Whatever happened to that Black boy?
He was good.
Stop. stop.
I actually wanted to. uh.
lay some groundwork
uh. to a pathway of. uh.
buying some of them back. Right?
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah. Totally.
Um...
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Actually. OJ. the offer
I made your dad is still on the table.
Oh. uh...
- Let me...
- Yo. wait a minute.
So. that...
OJ. have I shown you this?
This is in reference
to the Gordy's Home! incident.
Gordy's Home!
Yeah. yeah.
So. Gordy's Home! is a short-lived
but fabled sitcom I starred in in '96
after Kid Sheriff blew up.
Yeah. my pops told me
about that show.
The monkey went crazy
or some shit.
You know.
I usually charge a fee for this.
Oh. damn.
Ta-da.
Hmm.
That's the first
exploding fist bump.
What? Really?
Y'all came up with that?
So. as I was saying. uh.
Gordy's Home! began airing
in the fall of '96...
and it was an immediate hit.
Uh. ratings were huge.
Pretty good reviews.
Just really took off.
Yeah.
Then. uh. one day...
we were shooting
an episode in season two
entitled. uh. "Gordy's Birthday."
and. um. boom.
One of the chimps that plays Gordy
just... just hit his limit.
And it was six minutes
and 13 seconds of havoc.
Network tried to bury it.
but it was a spectacle.
People are just obsessed.
You're kidding me. OJ.
you said you heard about that?
Mm-hmm. That's why
they don't let you use chimps.
That's part of the reason.
There's a growing Gordy's Home!
fan base out there now.
This Dutch couple paid me 50K
to come in here and spend the night.
I didn't ask.
That's crazy.
So what happened really. man?
You haven't seen
the "Bad Gordy" sketch on SNL?
I mean. they pretty much nailed it
better than I could.
- Mmm.
- No?
Saturday Night Live?
Darrell Hammond as Tom.
Ana Gasteyer as Phyllis.
Cheri Oteri is Mary Jo Elliott.
Scott Wolf is the host. He's me.
But. of course. the star of the sketch
is Chris-goddamn-Kattan as Gordy.
and he is... undeniable. okay?
Bit goes like this.
Everyone's trying to celebrate
Gordy's birthday.
but every time Gordy hears
something about the jungle.
Gordy... Kattan... goes off.
And it's... it's Kattan.
He's just crushing it.
He is a force of nature.
He is killing on that stage.
Yeah.
It was legendary.
Legendary shit.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'ma have to go ahead
and look that one up on YouTube.
Details. you know?
Totally.
I got some work I gotta do.
So we ain't gonna
chill tonight? Nothin'?
You wanna work?
Hell. no.
So. uh. what was the offer?
- Jupe?
- Yeah.
He offered to buy the ranch.
Oh. really?
That's interesting. How much?
Why?
'Cause. I'm trying to see
how big of a dumbass you are.
Big dumbass. probably.
I guess you don't wanna see what's good
with Dad liquor cabinet then. huh?
I got that hobby weed too.
actually.
- That's all you had to say. then.
- The hobby weed.
That's all you had to say.
You should've dropped that at the top.
"I got the hobby weed."
You know I'm ready.
♪ If you see me walking down the street ♪
♪ And I start to cry
Each time we meet... ♪
Okay. your reflexes are still quick.
Like. whoa. I ain't mad at it.
I'm watching.
- ♪ Walk on by ♪
- To the man.
♪ Make believe ♪
- ♪ That you don't see the fears ♪
- Drink.
♪ Just let me grieve in private... ♪
Oh. shit.
Remember Jean Jacket?
Yeah. good horse.
Supposed to be my first horse.
actually.
I was talking to my therapist
about this not long ago.
Therapist?
Yes.
I fuck one on occasion sometimes.
♪ Walk on by...
I was telling her that.
for my ninth birthday.
I was supposed to
get to train Jean Jacket.
But then Pops got some western.
and Jean Jacket wasn't mine no more.
Classic Otis Senior.
I distinctly remember...
standing right here at this window.
watching y'all train my horse.
My horse.
Pops never looked up at me.
Whoa. now.
Whoa. now. Whoa. now.
OJ. come on.
But you did. nigga.
Remember?
It was Scorpion King. actually.
It wasn't a western.
That was the first job
Pops took me on.
Wasn't much fun.
Ended up using camels anyways.
The point is...
Yeah. fuck the point.
Yo. that man was hardheaded as fuck.
And so are you.
That's it.
But at the end of the day. you gotta...
You gotta admit. man. Pops...
Pops did something
when he made this place.
He changed the industry.
That's real.
I can't just let that go.
Why is Ghost in the arena?
What's good?
Yeah.
Hey. yo. Em.
Em!
Turn it down!
- ♪ Your generation believed in talk ♪
- All right!
♪ Scared of the very steps in which... ♪
Hey!
Where he going?
What if I fold you...
What if I told you...
you'll leave here different?
You see. every Friday
for the last six months...
my family and I bore witness
to an absolute...
spectacle.
Huh?
You see it? The power?
Where's Ghost?
I don't know.
Hold on.
Boom.
Power went out.
- See?
- Rewind.
Stop.
Ghost talking about.
"I ain't listening. I'm not trained.
I do whatever the fuck I want."
What?
What'd you see?
What's a bad miracle?
Hmm?
They got a word for that?
No.
They said it was a prop plane
or something that killed Pops.
That shit ain't never
made sense to me.
Then tonight. I heard Ghost make a sound
I ain't never heard a horse make.
What did you see?
Hmm?
It was big.
- How big?
- Big.
- What did it look like?
- I don't know.
It was fast.
Too fast.
Too quiet to be a plane.
OJ...
are you saying
what I think you're saying?
I'm telling you.
we don't need a lot.
Just enough to make our shit look
different from what's out there.
You get what I'm saying? Like...
You know I ain't trying to run it up.
I just was looking online.
and I seen a lot of shit.
You know I'm broke. right?
We'll use my money.
Okay. shut up.
Look. All right.
There it is. Five to 100K.
Well. read it.
You read it! Dyslexic ass.
The point is. a website
like Cyber Dominion
will pay five to 100K for photographic
evidence of UFOs and shit.
100K?
And that's just what I saw
on the first go.
Now that I've been thinking about it.
fuck Cyber Dominion.
This shit right here is a moment.
Our moment.
We set it up.
release it the right way...
Man. I'm talking
rich and famous for life.
How you doing?
You look pretty.
- She looks like she got a big house.
- How?
- How we put it out?
- Mmm.
That's what I'm saying.
We don't just go
for the quick cash-in. okay?
We go to the most credible platform
to do the story.
What's that? Like Oprah?
Yeah. Like Oprah. for example.
After that. everybody want in.
I'm saying there's plenty of videos
of flying shit online.
I saw one the other day.
That wasn't on Oprah.
Nigga. I didn't say Oprah.
You said Oprah.
You love Oprah.
Look. all I'm saying is.
all that shit online is fake.
Low quality. Ain't nobody
gonna get what we gonna get.
- What we gonna get?
- The shot.
What shot?
The shot. The money shot.
Undeniable. Singular...
The Oprah shot.
The Oprah shot?
Excuse me.
Hi. I can help you over here.
Hi. Thank you for shopping at Fry's.
Did you find everything
you were looking for?
Yes. Angel.
Oh. Great.
- Um. do you have a card with us?
- No. thank you.
- Would you like one? Because it...
Would you like one of
our tech-support personnel
to help with installation?
No. no. no. Thank you.
Appreciate you.
All right.
Uh. no help with the install.
Suit yourself.
Is it a hard install?
Well. for me. no.
You're not gonna be able to do it.
What happened?
Did you guys get robbed?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah. You know. a lot of blackouts.
Take the camera out
from time to time.
All these new cameras
have backup battery power.
so you should be fine.
But the outages affect the power
in the battery shit too. like cell phones.
Okay. All right.
Cell phones. they don't
just drop in power. Right?
I mean. maybe your Wii-Fi drops out
whenever your system dips.
So. that's technology.
Okay. Or maybe you're in
a UFO hotspot.
No one believes in that.
What's up?
Damn. Did not realize you guys
were this far out.
Mm-hmm.
I don't mind. though.
Smell of horseshit and fresh air.
Right?
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
- Whoa. Look at me. man.
- Fuck.
- Don't do that. Don't yell.
- Sorry. man.
Sorry if I was shut down
this morning.
I just got out of
a four-year relationship.
You were fine.
I know it's gonna sound
fucking cliché.
but I thought that
she was the one. you know?
Is this gonna take
longer than an hour?
This?
Oh. shit. yeah.
- 'Ma go ahead and pop out.
- Where you gong?
I gotta go to the store and get something.
Don't worry about it. You need anything?
Yo.
Her name was. uh. Rebecca Diaz.
Yeah. keep an eye out for her.
She's an actress. model.
you know?
She booked a pilot
on the CW. so...
Yeah. fucking left me.
Yeah. fucking CW.
- So. thing about this camera...
- Actually. can it swivel up?
Uh. yeah.
Boom.
Little more?
More? Okay.
Yeah.
Mmm.
All right. Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
Do you know they don't call 'em
UFOs anymore?
It's fucking UAPs now.
Why they gotta change the name?
Yeah. Exactly.
No. fuck it. I'll tell you why
they changed the name. all right?
It's 'cause they wanna
keep us in the dark.
Remember when they declassified
all that UFO footage a couple years ago?
Yeah. Well. people started
paying attention.
So they changed the name
to UAPs.
And no one knows
what the fuck a UAP is.
So everyone lost interest.
I saw that. that navy clip.
Couldn't really see 'em. though.
Could've been better.
It's shitty footage of exact proof
that there's an alien civilization
out there in the universe.
So who's that?
Come on. man.
The little guys with the big eyes.
- Mmm.
- Yeah. There's lots of theories.
Either they're intergalactic travelers
looking for peace
or futuristic humans
coming back in time to stop us
from destroying the planet.
or they're fucking
world-killers.
Planetary destroyers.
And that means that they've been
fucking watching us and studying us.
waiting for the perfect time
to beam us up
and shove metal probes
up our fucking asses.
Cool.
Anyway. Ancient Aliens.
History Channel. Watch that shit.
Hey!
Come on! Help a nigga out!
Hey.
Know where I could find me
a couple of big. strong fellas?
You good?
I'm good.
- What?
- What's that?
Oh. this?
You know. just. uh. training horses
we ordered that I picked up.
Where'd you get it from?
Don't worry about it.
Now. come on. help me out.
Got you.
Okay. so what is it?
Is it like bait?
I told you. It is a decoy
for horse training.
Okay.
Shit. Shit.
- See?
- OJ.
We good.
I mean. he don't know shit.
Oh. no. You guys are
doing something shady.
Hey. there!
Hey!
You can stay right there. though!
Sure!
What's up?
We setting up a decoy
for horse training!
Oh. good!
You know. we got some of those.
- Where'd you get...
- Where'd you get yours?
Yeah. I'm not really sure.
My wife would know.
- Okay! Thanks for stopping by!
- Shh! You don't live here.
- Sorry. Trying to help.
- Sure thing!
Hey. I wanted to invite you to our...
new family live show.
Friday at 5:00 p.m.
Okay!
Thumbs... Thumbs up!
- Should I do it?
- Yeah. do it.
Thumbs up!
So. the router's in the shed.
I set it up so if the power goes out
on camera A.
camera B's pointed at the sky
to catch whatever might've taken it out.
And. uh. vice versa. So...
Thank you.
You're really not gonna tell
what the fuck is going on?
- You'll know soon enough.
- Oh.
Cool. cryptic.
Fucking dicks.
I can monitor the feeds remotely
myself if you want. Free of charge.
- Hell. no.
- No.
Wham. bam. thank you. ma'am.
One more thing.
You'll be getting a call from
my supervisor asking how my service was.
Five stars. Angel. Five stars.
Thank you.
- So what now?
- I don't know. What you wanna do?
- Whatever you wanna do.
- I got some work I gotta do.
I'm gonna go out...
That's a good one.
♪ Fisherman. row ♪
♪ Keep on rowing your boat ♪
♪ Brother man. brother man. yeah. row... ♪
I'm talking today to women
who say they have been abducted
by aliens from another planet.
May I say. I don't know
for a fact they're from another planet.
Well. you know.
you weren't in Kansas anymore. Toto.
I wasn't wearing
red shoes I could click together either.
♪ Living in a bamboo hut ♪
♪ In a little old seaport town ♪
♪ Three kids on the floor... ♪
Nope. Mm-mmm. Nope. I'm out.
Fuck this shit.
Okay. Okay.
Ow!
- Oh. shit!
- Fuck off.
Give us back our property.
Don't mess with Jupiter's Claim!
Hey. what happened?
The Park kids. Jupe's sons.
And they let Clover out. man.
What? They trying to
prank Haywood? It's on!
Hey. you stole their horse.
Oh. Yeah.
- Hey.
- Shit.
Oh.
What's up. Nessie?
Not much. Just stocking shit.
You know. pretty much regular.
Oh. shit!
I need to take my ass to bed.
- Who dis?
- Yo. its Angel from Fry's.
Just calling to tell you
that there's a bug on camera A.
I know. Wait. I thought
I told you not to watch our shit.
I know. I know.
- Camera B is down.
- What?
Camera B is down.
Like Ancient fucking Aliens down.
- Hey!
- Hey. hi.
Emerald. can you please get
the bug off the thing?
Get the bug
off the fucking thing!
Shit.
Um. what do you see?
Do you see. like. lights or anything?
Like a... a fucking saucer?
It's in the cloud. It's in the cloud.
OJ! It's in the cloud!
Mm-hmm.
Yeah. nah. nah. nah.
Run. OJ! Run!
Hello?
What happened to OJ?
It's fine.
Come on.
Okay. it's still on.
The camera. it's still on.
Shit. shit. shit. shit. shit.
Okay. you fucking praying mantis.
All right. bitch.
You like Sour Patch Kids?
Huh?
Aight. man.
Where your shit? Let's go.
- Haven't seen one of those in a minute.
- Fucking praying mantis.
That motherfucker better pray
I don't ever see him.
'cause if I do. 'ma eat him.
- Let's go.
- Where?
I don't know.
I got me a little situation
in Atwater texting me back right now.
- It's not coming again tonight.
- I don't care.
No.
Bro. I ain't never seen
no shit like this.
It ain't worth it.
No. Nope.
It's too much.
You should go. then.
I gotta get up early anyway.
I got mouths to feed.
Shit.
Shit. shit. shit.
You hear that?
Ghost out there.
Acting all territorial.
Mmm.
I guess some animals
ain't fit to be trained.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Is this. uh. Antlers Holst?
Who's this?
Hey. yeah. I'm Emerald Haywood.
We met a couple days ago
at the commercial.
Oh. yeah. Horse girl. Sure.
I remember you and your brother.
Yeah. horse boy.
He's here too.
- The descendants of the jockey.
- Yeah.
Guess I'm talking to
motion-picture royalty then.
How'd you get the number?
I got it from the call sheet.
- Ah.
- So. we have a project. And. uh.
you know. what if I told you
it was the offer of a lifetime?
Yeah. hopefully not my lifetime.
That's a good one.
Um. 'ma be real with you.
We don't have a lot of money
to pay you up front...
Not like you're used to... but. uh...
Yeah. I tend to do one for them.
so I can do one for me.
So. what is it?
Reality.
- Oh. no. Reality.
- Documentary.
- Doc... Documentary.
- Oh. that's better.
So again. whats it about?
It's about the shit
dreams is made of. baby.
Listen. horse girl.
I got a. uh.
pretty damn superb lemon tart
in the oven
that I'm about to serve
to ten of my closest friends. so...
Stop. Stop. stop.
Oh. hold on one second. What?
He's not here for that.
- No. This is what I do.
- Stick to the plan.
I don't go to your job
and knock a horse's dick out your hand.
- Hello?
- Yeah?
Yeah. my bad.
We good. man.
Um. according to
American Cinema magazine.
you make the cinematically
impossible possible.
Well. we looking for
the impossible shot.
That's impossible.
Antlers.
there's something out here
in Agua Dulce.
and you're probably the only person
in the world that can get it on film.
That's it.
Horse girl.
this dream you're chasing.
the one where you end up
at the top of the mountain.
all eyes on you...
It's the dream you never wake up from.
I don't like him.
Holy shit. It's real.
I don't know
what you're doing here. but...
it was illegal for you
to spy on us like that.
Wait. you... you don't know?
Okay. uh. tell me when you see it.
There.
- Doesn't move.
- Exactly.
Well. look at that.
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. okay.
I went back and scrubbed
through the footage.
and that cloud has been right there
at least since I set the cameras up.
Yeah. now you mention it.
I've probably been looking at the same
cloud every day for the last six months.
Shit.
So. I mean. that's them in there.
And we've been recording it.
so we got it. right?
Yeah.
Why you saying "yeah" like that?
I mean. we have proof
of aliens on video.
Yeah. I wouldn't call it "proof."
Are you serious?
Look. I've seen crazy weather
phenomenons online before.
He's right.
It's good. but it ain't it. Ain't Oprah.
Ain't Oprah.
Okay.
Are you guys telling me
that there's an alien spaceship
in that fucking cloud right there?
It doesn't move like a ship.
What you mean. OJ?
What if it's not a ship?
All right. Gordy.
We're almost ready. buddy.
Wake up. buddy. Come on.
He's ready.
Here we go. And action!
And. of course.
I set it to Icelandic time.
because we share a love
of the aurora borealis. Gordy.
And you have no idea how to tell time.
Great gift. Dad.
Way to think things through.
Somehow you'd think that a man
who can send a rocket into space
would be able to manage
a halfway decent birthday present.
Nope.
You know. Gordy.
all things considered.
maybe my gift isn't so bad after all.
Aw.
Hey. Gordy!
- Surprise!
- Wow!
Now. that is a gift!
Oh. sorry.
That's all right.
Pick it up from there.
Wait a minute.
What happened to we both failed
at finding good presents?
Here you go. Gordy. Happy birthday!
Oh. beautiful. Haley!
No. no! Get down!
- No. Stop!
- Stop that!
No. no. no.
No. no. no. Gordy. No.
No!
Down! Down! You sit!
No. no. no!
No. Gordy! No. please.
Stop! No. no. no.
Oh. my God.
Yeah. it's pretty bad in here.
Feeling good?
Yeah.
- Feeling good.
- Good.
There we go.
Run it. Run it
one more time. babe.
Okay.
What if I told you...
Yo. So. a storm's coming.
Just tarping up.
Just to be safe.
Hey. where you going?
I'ma get Lucky.
Now we're not gonna let a few
clouds kill our fun today. are we. folks?
So. without further ado.
welcome to the Jupiter's Claim
Star Lasso Experience!
How's everyone feeling today?
All right!
It's quite a doozy today.
Uh. I wanna thank you guys
for coming out here. but first.
how about another round of applause
for my Amber?
I'll tell you. that woman is a saint
for putting up with all my craziness.
And to the knuckleheads up there.
the staff. shout-out.
All right. all right. that's enough.
I also wanna give a special thanks
to an old costar of mine.
and my first crush.
Mary Jo Elliott. everyone!
Yeah!
All right.
You ready?
Oh. come on. That ain't nothin'.
Are you ready?
Here we go.
You're chosen.
What if I told you.
in about an hour.
you'll leave here different?
See. every Friday
for the last six months.
my family and I have bore witness
to an absolute spectacle.
One that you'll be seeing here today.
So let me take you back
to that first night.
Right here. in this exact spot.
I come over to wrangle a chestnut horse
named Trigger.
Now. I could barely see my hand
in front of my face for the fog.
but I swear on my wife
and children's lives
that at 6:13 p.m..
I see...
a flying saucer descend
through the mist.
Old Trigger took off
straight into the gulch.
And. well.
it's like he was going home.
Now. just to be clear.
what we saw was a flying saucer.
No doubt about that.
Slightly flatter in the front.
with a circular hole in the bottom
about two school bus lengths wide.
Ladies and gentlemen. I kid you not.
We are being surveilled
by an alien species I call the Viewers.
And though they have yet
to emerge from their ship.
I believe they trust me.
If they didn't.
I don't think any of us
would be here right now.
So. as I said.
in just under an hour.
Star Lasso Experience
is gonna change you.
But first. my boys are gonna come out
and do a little number for us.
- Would that be all right?
- Hustle. Go. go. go.
All right! My little satellites.
Kolton. Phoenix. Max.
Remember those names. folks.
All right. here we go!
What is that?
You guys see that?
Uh. uh. stay in your seats.
This is new. Uh. they're early.
They're giving us a real show today.
That they are.
They're ready. we're ready.
Welcome to the Star Lasso Experience.
only at Jupiter's Claim.
Please remember to avoid using
your cell phones
- or flash photography during the event.
- Cell phones off. y'all!
Come on!
Bear with us. now.
Trained animals can be unpredictable.
Now. sit back.
stay in your seats. and enjoy
the Star Lasso Experience.
Well. cowboys and cowgirls.
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right. Happy trails.
Its closing time.
You don't have to go home.
but you can't stay here.
Come back again.
Until then. we wish you well.
Hasta la vista. Adios.
Well. cowboys and cowgirls.
it's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right. Happy trails.
Its closing time.
You don't have to go home.
but you can't stay here.
Come back again. Until then...
Lucky.
Lucky. come on. come on.
Come on.
- Come on. come on.
- Come on. Lucky!
Come on. come on. come on.
Yo. It's done.
I'll be over in the morning
to tear that shit off.
- Or you can do it yourselves.
- No. no. I like when you do it.
Of course you do.
All right.
See you tomorrow.
See ya.
Pick up. pick up. pick up.
Come on. come on.
Did you know that
the very first assembly of photographs
in sequential order
to make a motion picture
was a two-second clip
of a Black man on a horse?
That man was a Bahamian jockey
known as Alistair E. Haywood.
and he was my great-great-grandfather.
- Hey.
- Em!
I was right.
It's not a ship.
What happened?
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ So I can. so... ♪
What the fuck?
Shit.
It ate them. Em.
It ate them all.
It's alive. Em. It's an animal.
It's territorial.
and it thinks that this is its...
Em!
Oh. shit.
Oh. yes.
Hey. hey. We're in trouble.
Oh. fuck.
What?
What the fuck?
Who the hell is that?
Oh. my God.
Em! Who the hell is that?
It's above us.
Oh. shit.
Oh. shit. What the fuck?
Oh. God.
Something very bad is happening.
Fuck!
Em. we're fucked.
Nope.
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ So I can... ♪
♪ It cuts my security ♪
♪ Has she got control of me? ♪
♪ I turn to her and say... ♪
Em? OJ's coming.
Let's go.
I gotta get out this house.
No. stop. stop.
Can't we just wait? Right?
- You can.
- No. I'm not gonna be here alone.
- I gotta get out of this fucking house!
- We're alive still because we stayed here!
Shit.
♪ I wear my sunglasses... ♪
- Let's go!
- Come on.
Go!
Come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Come on. come on.
Oh. shit.
Go.
Yeah. She gonna make it.
- OJ.
- She gonna make it.
Oh. hey. horsie.
- Don't look it in the eyes. please.
- VEX!
Focus here. Focus here.
- ♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
- Go!
♪ I wear my sunglasses at night ♪
♪ I cry to you... ♪
Welcome to my tavern.
I don't know if you've heard.
but a terrible beast is about.
It's been harassing villagers.
ruining crops and eating their livestock.
Many a glory-seeking hunter
has attempted to defeat it.
and just as many have perished.
While you're here. please look around.
I'm here in Agua Dulce. California.
and the whereabouts
of those 40 guests and employees
of a local western theme park
are still unknown.
The sheriffs office has its hands full
trying to identify the unaccounted-for.
Until they do. only one thing is certain:
There is something strange happening
out here in Agua Dulce.
Security cameras were off at the time.
Other than that. we have. uh.
no reason to suspect foul play.
We did have a considerable amount
of rain come through here.
So we don't wanna rule out flash flooding
as possibly having played a part.
You never go wrong
with a fried-fish sandwich.
Tartar got tang.
Stupid.
"Tartar got tang"?
Right?
I don't think it eats you
if you don't look it in the eye.
Hey. hey!
RTR. bro.
You know?
Like. read the room.
Nobody wanna talk about that.
- Let's go.
- Okay. okay. Enough.
All right. all right. all right.
Hey. you lucky!
Every animal got rules. right?
We know what it wants.
and we know how it comes. so...
Fuck.
We don't really know shit.
OJ. what's this about. man?
What's this about? You want me to...
You want me to say. "I'm sorry"?
"I was wrong. It's dumb"?
It wasn't. though.
- Own the moment.
- Stop.
- It was good. It was good.
- Stop this shit!
But the moment about to pass.
and we don't own shit.
Okay. well. I assume
y'all are crashing at mine.
Right? 'Cause you can.
'Cause I'm not going back
to the fuckin' monster umbrella.
Gotta feed 'em.
Let Lucky out.
There's shit to do.
Always.
Always some shit to do.
There's a wheelchair
on your roof.
Hi.
That cloud ain't moved
a goddamn inch.
So you're not completely full of shit.
- Thank you.
- Yeah. Thank you.
The concept
of extraterrestrial animals in the sky
is not a new thing.
People have been trying to get pictures
of these things since the '50s.
How do we see it?
It's gonna get hungry again.
Huh.
So. you know.
just ring the dinner bell.
Now. we know what it doesn't like.
That little fake horse and flags
messed it up good.
Got stuck in its windpipes or something.
I bet he ain't gonna
fuck with flags like that in a minute.
Yeah.
We pissed him off.
We're not the reason
it settled down here.
That was Jupe. He got caught up
trying to tame a predator.
You can't do that.
You gotta enter an agreement with one.
Yeah.
Ask Siegfried and Roy.
Okay. um.
asking as someone who was
in the house when the shit went down...
Mmm.
how exactly do you enter
an agreement with a fucking...
a UFO. alien entity.
or whatever the hell you wanna call it?
Jean Jacket.
- Call him Jean Jacket.
- So. how about this?
How about we send old Jean Jacket
some fresh horses in golden hour
and see what happens?
Mm-mmm.
Horse people.
- Mmm. Why not just set them free?
- We're not doing that.
Okay.
Who is gonna go down there
and get the star out of his trailer?
Me.
I'll get him out.
Where you want it?
You draw him out there.
I'm here.
On this ridge.
Oh. shit.
Made her myself. No electricity.
Didn't I tell you this motherfucker
was gonna come up here
with a non-electrical camera?
Let's go. boy!
I've been up under it
a couple times now.
I get him.
It's an animal.
You don't turn your back on a bear.
You don't wear red around a bull.
It's like that.
You don't look at it
unless you want its attention.
Good night. Mr. Storeman.
Fuck it. I call the top hat.
And we ain't got a lot of time.
One day. Two days. tops.
'Cause the word's getting out.
and when it does...
Sorry. dead people.
Park's closed.
you know people gonna come
and do what they always do:
Try and take it all for themselves.
Fine.
Thimble.
That's the one I wanted anyway.
Well. let 'em come.
It ain't gonna matter.
'Cause what we about to do...
they can't erase that.
He's big.
he's mad.
and he's got a lot of spirit.
But anything with a spirit can get broke.
So you break it.
I'll get the shot.
Hey. I don't know.
What we're doing is
important. right?
Like. what we document.
it's. uh...
It's gonna do some good. Huh?
I mean. besides the money
and fucking fame.
we can save some lives.
Fuck. we... we can even save Earth.
Right?
- Mmm.
- Yeah.
Well. it came down to Earth.
and it hid in a tree.
I said. "Mr. Purple People Eater.
don't eat me."
Well. he looked at me.
and in a voice so gruff...
he said. "I wouldn't eat you.
'cause you're too tough."
"He was a one-eyed. one-horned
flyin' purple people eater.
One-eyed. one-horned
Sure looks strange to me."
He ain't gonna fuck with you.
Time to wake up the family.
Here we go.
Come out. come out. wherever you are.
♪ I came down on a lightning bolt ♪
♪ Nine months in my mama's belly ♪
♪ When I was born
The midwife screamed and shout ♪
♪ I had fire and brimstone
Coming out of my mouth... ♪
How exquisitely stupid is that?
♪ Na-Na-Na. Na-Na-Na ♪
♪ Na-Na. Na-Na-Na ♪
♪ Exuma was my name
When I lived in the stars ♪
♪ Exuma was a planet that once lit Mars ♪
♪ I got the voices of many in my throat ♪
♪ The teeth of a frog
And the tail of a goat ♪
♪ I'm Exuma ♪
♪ I'm the obeah man... ♪
♪ Na-Na-Na. Na-Na-Na ♪
♪ Na-Na-Na. Na-Na-Na... ♪
We gonna get you today. motherfucker.
- ♪ When I've got my ♪
- ♪ Obeah ♪
- ♪ Big hat on my head ♪
- ♪ You know that I ♪
- ♪ Obeah ♪
- ♪ Can raise the dead ♪
♪ And when I got my stick in my hand ♪
♪ You know that am... ♪
Where is the feed for Holst's camera?
Over.
Couldn't figure it out. Over.
What you mean.
you couldn't figure it out? Over.
Um. Holst is shooting
on a film camera.
and all of our cameras are digital.
So its a whole thing. Over.
Basically.
you forgot about it. Over.
I had my hands full
rigging 50 fucking skydancers
to dead people's car batteries.
all connected to one control panel.
So. yeah. fucking over.
Sorry. Scared.
Man down.
- Man down? What? Where?
- The last dancer. Deep in the gulch.
Stay on it. Em. I'm staying up.
Motherfucker.
Oh. wait.
Oh. it's back up.
Could be a faulty battery.
All right. Shots up. then.
Nah. he's poking.
Who's this asshole?
Man in black
on a white motorcycle.
No. no. no. Shit!
Can I help you?
You see that cloud?
Hey. man. who you with?
Oh. I'm sorry.
Who are you?
Nobody.
You don't look like a nobody to me.
Yeah. look. we doing a camera test
for a Verizon commercial.
so I'ma need you to clear the road.
This whole valley comes up as blurry
on Google Maps.
You're really tucked away back here.
Jupiter's Claim?
Quicker if you go
the other way around.
Yeah.
Actually.
what did happen with Jupe Park
and all those people?
He was basically your neighbor. right?
So. what? They vanished?
You don't believe
the flood narrative. do you?
Fuck. guys. It's TMZ.
Oh. fuck me.
Uh. hey. guys.
Uh. Jean Jacket
is definitely in those clouds.
and he's definitely coming this way.
What's the matter?
Don't you wanna be on TV?
Man. I'm trying to tell you.
You don't wanna go that way.
Fuck it. Your loss. nobody.
We still rolling? Over.
Goddamn right. we are.
Fellas. here it comes. Over.
Pop quiz. guys.
What happens when an electric bike
going 60 miles per hour
hits an anti-electric field
going in the opposite direction?
Shit.
- Fuck. All right.
- Shit. We're all gonna go to jail.
Oh. fuck. There's no way
that that guy's alive.
Ah. shit.
Goddamn!
I told his ass not to go.
I told him not to go.
I Uh. hey. OJ. whats...
Where the fuck are you going?
What the fuck is he doing?
I'm going dark. Over.
Okay. No. OJ. No. No!
No self-respecting nigga...
Whoa. whoa. whoa. Hey. hey. Easy.
Did you get that on camera?
Look at me.
Look at me. Look at me.
- What happened?
- Listen. We gotta get you outta here.
- Eyes on me.
- Where's my camera?
- Hey. Hey!
- I need my camera. Do you see it?
- Okay. Angel.
- What?
Angel. come on.
We gotta reload.
Shit.
Wait.
Uh. where's your phone?
Why aren't you filming this?
Angel. what's happening?
Okay.
OJ. if you die trying
to save that guy. I'll kill you.
No. No. no. Please.
- Please don't.
- Shut your eye.
- Not before you take a picture.
Take a picture first.
Uh. camera reloads.
- You can use my camera.
- There's not enough time.
It's here.
Scorpion King.
make a name for yourself.
What is that?
My bad. man.
Hey. Oh. my God!
My camera! I need my camera!
What the fuck?
Give me the lid.
All right.
Oh. fuck! Shit! Fuck!
Hey! Hey! Is everybody okay?
For the love of fuck.
talk to me. please!
OJ!
OJ. OJ!
You stupid-ass motherfucker.
you better answer me.
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
Are you okay?
Are you good?
OJ/
Oh. God! Oh. God!
Oh. God!
Holy shit!
I think it's taking the dancers.
Are you getting this?
Guys. OJ's hooded up.
He's doing the run.
OJ's doing the run.
Oh. God.
Hey. its gone.
I can't see it anymore. guys.
Get it. Get it.
No!
Fuck!
Go! Go!
Lucky. go. Go. go. go. go. go.
Holy shit!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Yeah. he didn't like that. did he?
OJ. you're a motherfucking genius.
We got it. We got it.
It's over. It's over! We got it. y'all!
The feed started going in and out
when that guy got got.
But we should be covered
with the film camera.
Right. Holst?
The light...
The light. It's...
gonna be magic soon.
What do you mean. Ant?
No. no. Where are you going?
It's gonna be all right. Angel.
We don't deserve the impossible.
I Uh. hey. guys.
Holst just said
some creepy. cryptic shit.
Took his camera
and is headin' up the mountain.
Over.
Hey. Holst?
Holst?
Wait. hold on. man. Talk to me.
What happened?
Did you get the shot or didn't you? Over.
This nigga.
Fuck him.
He's crazy. right?
Come on. come on.
No. man.
What the fuck?
Holst.
Oh. shit.
Oh. fuck!
Oh.
Oh. God.
Oh. shit.
Fuck.
Okay.
Fuck!
Don't look. Don't look. Don't look.
Get the bike
and get outta here.
Oh. my God!
You're dead! Dead!
Bang.
Come on!
No.
Oh. fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
No!
I gotta get outta here.
Just leave. OJ.
Forget it. Come on!
Come on!
It's gonna fuck you up.
Come on.
Come on. come on!
What the...
Come on. Come on!
I got you now. motherfucker.
I'ma take you to Oprah.
Let's go to Oprah.
Yes!
Nobody fucks with Haywood. bitch!
Nobody! You hear me?
Cowboys and cowgirls.
It's time to ride off into the sunset.
That's right. Happy trails.
It's closing time.
You don't have to go home.
but you can't stay here.
Come back again.
and until then. we wish you well.
Hasta la vista. Adios.